We have got this telematic device with the ICICI car insurance policy.
Inside this device, we will find an OD port.
This is the OD
port. To use it, we will have to
enter the odometer reading here first.
We enter the odometer reading first.
Before continuing, please subscribe to this channel.
Then,
we have to click on this icon of the photo which is 'Design' here.
After clicking here, we have to take a photo of the window meter with the camera
and click on 'Use Photo'.
After this, click on 'Add'. After this, it will be
set.
Now, once the OD port
device is here, we will scan
it. See, it has automatically captured this number here.
After this, we have to
fix it in the OD port of the car.
Click
next. Now let's install it. This
white colored device that you see is the
OD port of the car. We have to install this device here. It is
very easy to install it. See,
see how to install it and push it properly.
It is fixed. Now, we will open the oil top.
Here we will get to know all the details of the vehicle.
First of all we see the live function from
where we will get the location of both ourselves and the car.
Like when we click on live,
first we see our own location, my
location. If we want to see the location of the vehicle, then
click on this track.
As soon as we click on this track,
we will get the location of the vehicle. This is the
location of the vehicle. If we click on this icon, then we will get to know the
network details.
Then if we click on this workshop, then
we will get to know all the available workshop shops near the location of our car.
This is it. Other options: Trip
data is still nothing, so we will
see the activity now because the vehicle has
run only once so far. After applying this,
see this, our vehicle has run 7 km in 20 minutes.
If we click on this, then we will also
see the start and end point of this trip. See, we get the details of the start and end point also.
Before exploring other options, please subscribe to this channel.
If we click on Negate to Car, then
we will get the route from our location
to the location of the vehicle.  You will
get the distance, it directs us to that place, there are
many other options in this,
driving summary etc. etc., so through this you will get the
drive score of your drive, thank you.